Guide to the Faculty Minutes RG.018
Poly Archives at the Bern Dibner Library of Science and Technology, NYU Libraries
- Series III: Boxes, 1986 - present; 6668
  - Faculty Minutes, May 4, 2011, 6947 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 4, 2011 (duplicates), 6948 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 4, 2011 (duplicates), 6949 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 5, 2011, 6950 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 5, 2011 (duplicates), 6951 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 14, 2011, 6952 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 14, 2011 (duplicates), 6953 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 17, 2011, 6954 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 17, 2011 (duplicates), 6955 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 24, 2011, 6956 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 24, 2011 (duplicates), 6957 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 2, 2011, 6958 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 2, 2011 (duplicates), 6959 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 7, 2011, 6960 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 7, 2011 (duplicates), 6961 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 1, 2012, 6962 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 1, 2012 (duplicates), 6963 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2012, 6964 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 7, 2012 (duplicates), 6965 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 4, 2012, 6966 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 4, 2012 (duplicates), 6967 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2012, 6968 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 2, 2012 (duplicates), 6969 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 12, 2012, 6970 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 12, 2012 (duplicates), 6971 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 3, 2012, 6972 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 3, 2012 (duplicates), 6973 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 7, 2012, 6974 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 7, 2012 (duplicates), 6975 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 5, 2012, 6976 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Minutes, December 5, 2012 (duplicates), 6977 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 6, 2013, 6978 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Faculty Minutes, February 6, 2013 (duplicates), 6979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 6, 2013, 6980 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Minutes, March 6, 2013 (duplicates), 6981 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Faculty Mintues, April 10, 2013, 6982 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Faculty Minutes, April 10, 2013 (duplicates), 6983 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 1, 2013, 6984 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Faculty Minutes, May 1, 2013 (duplicates), 6985 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Faculty Minutes, September 11, 2013, 6986 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Faculty Mintues, September 11, 2013 (duplicates), 6987 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Faculty Minutes, October 2, 2013, 6988 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 6, 2013, 7037 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Faculty Minutes, November 6, 2013 (duplicates), 7038 (Box 21, Folder 21)